Guide to the Edward G. and Hortense R. Levy Autograph Collection, Part Two
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Autograph Items by Category, 1666-1961; Series I; 12.1; (32 boxes)
  - ARTISTS
    - Virtue, George, 1793?-1868, 1861 (Box 5, Folder 308)
    - Waterlow, Ernest A., Sir, 1850-1919, 1903, undated (Box 5, Folder 309)
    - Waterman, Marcus, b. 1834, 1900 (Box 5, Folder 310)
    - Whistler, James McNeill, 1834-1903, 1889 (Box 5, Folder 311)
    - Woods, Henry, 1846-1921, 1905 (Box 5, Folder 312)
    - Yeames, William Frederick, 1835-1918, 1890-1905 (Box 5, Folder 313)
  - AUTHORS
    - A Beckett, Gilbert, 1837-1891, 1886 (Box 6, Folder 314)
    - Aide, Hamilton, 1826-1906, undated (Box 6, Folder 315)
    - Amberley, John Russell, Viscount, 1843-1876, 1872 (Box 6, Folder 316)
    - Anson, William Reynell, Sir, 1843-1914, 1899-1910 (Box 6, Folder 317)
    - Arnold, Edwin, Sir, 1832-1904, 1895 (Box 6, Folder 318)
    - Austin, Alfred, 1835-1913, undated (Box 6, Folder 319)
    - Bagehot, Walter, 1826-1877 (Box 6, Folder 320)
    - Balfour, Alice Blanche, 1908 (Box 6, Folder 321)
    - Birch, Samuel, 1813-1885, 1870 (Box 6, Folder 322)
    - Blinde, Mathilde, 1841-1896, undated (Box 6, Folder 323)
    - Bowring, John, Sir, 1792-1872, 1847, undated (Box 6, Folder 324)
    - Brewer, Ebenezer Cobham, 1810-1897, 1850 (Box 6, Folder 325)
    - Browning, Elizabeth Barrett, 1806-1861, undated (Box 6, Folder 326)
    - Bryden, H.A. (Henry Anderson), 1854- 1937, 1901-10 (Box 6, Folder 327)
    - Buckingham, James Silk, 1786-1855, 1843-50, undated (Box 6, Folder 328)
    - Buckle, George Earle, 1854-1935, 1889-1903, undated (Box 6, Folder 329)
    - Burdette, Robert J. (Robert Jones), 1844-1914, 1905 (Box 6, Folder 330)
    - Butler, Henry Montagu, 1833-1918, 1898 (Box 6, Folder 331)
    - Butler, Nicholas Murray, 1862-1947, 1929 (Box 6, Folder 332)
    - Carr, John, 1732-1807, 1801 (Box 6, Folder 333)
    - Chorley, Henry Fothergill, 1808-1872, 1865 (Box 6, Folder 334)
    - Clark, Hyde, 1815-1895, 1854-93, undated (Box 6, Folder 335)
    - Clayden, P.W. (Peter William), 1827- 1902, 1880-97 (Box 6, Folder 336)
    - Cobb, Irvin S. (Irvin Shrewsbury), 1876-1944, 1941, undated (Box 6, Folder 337)
    - Cohen, Chapman, b. 1868, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 338)
    - Cook, Eliza, 1881-1889, undated (Box 6, Folder 339)
    - Crockett, S.R. (Samuel Rutherford), 1860-1914, undated (Box 6, Folder 340)
    - Crowe, Catherine, 1800?-1876, undated (Box 6, Folder 341)
    - Delane, John Thaddeus, 1817-1879, 1856-74, undated (Box 6, Folder 342)
    - Doyle, Arthur Conan, Sir, 1859-1930, 1913-27 (Box 6, Folder 343)
    - Edgeworth, Maria, 1767-1849, undated (Box 6, Folder 344)
    - Ellis, Sarah Stickney, 1812-1872, undated (Box 6, Folder 345)
    - Ewing, Juliana Horatia Gatty, 1841- 1885, undated (Box 6, Folder 346)
    - Faber, Frederick William, 1814-1863, undated (Box 6, Folder 347)
    - Farrar, Frederic William, 1831-1903, 1892-94, undated (Box 6, Folder 348)
    - Ferguson, Samuel, Sir, 1810-1886, 1878 (Box 6, Folder 349)
    - Fergusson, James, 1808-1886, 1875 (Box 6, Folder 350)
    - Forster, E.M. (Edward Morgan), 1879- 1970, undated (Box 6, Folder 351)
    - Forster, John, 1812-1876, 1856-73, undated (Box 6, Folder 352)
    - Friedlaender, Helen, 1929 (Box 6, Folder 353)
    - Froude, James Anthony, 1818-1894, 1867, undated (Box 6, Folder 354)
    - Fyleman, Rose, 1877-1957, undated (Box 6, Folder 355)
    - Galpin, Thomas D., 1887 (Box 6, Folder 356)
    - Garvice, Charles, 1833-1920, undated (Box 6, Folder 357)
    - Gollancz, Israel, Sir, 1864-1930, 1908-11 (Box 6, Folder 358)
    - Hall, Basil, 1788-1844, 1838 (Box 7, Folder 359)
    - Hall, S.C. (Samuel Carter), 1800-1889, undated (Box 7, Folder 360)
    - Hall, S.C., Mrs., 1800-1881, 1845 (Box 7, Folder 361)
    - Harness, William, 1790-1869, 1866-72 (Box 7, Folder 362)
    - Harrison, Mary St. Leger Kingsley, 1852-1931, 1910 (Box 7, Folder 363)
    - Hayward, A. (Abraham), 1801-1884, 1867, undated (Box 7, Folder 364)
    - Herbert, Auberon Edward William Molyneux, Hon., 1838-1906, 1884-1901, undated (Box 7, Folder 365)
    - Hope, Anthony, 1863-1933, 1896-1902, undated (Box 7, Folder 366)
    - Hoskins, Oliver Hevwood, 1837 (Box 7, Folder 367)
    - Hotten, John Camden, 1832-1873, 1865 (Box 7, Folder 368)
    - Jacobs, W.W. (William Wymark), 1863- 1943, undated (Box 7, Folder 369)
    - Jay, William, 1769-1853, 1825 (Box 7, Folder 370)
    - Jeremiah, John, 1873-96 (Box 7, Folder 371)
    - Jerome, Jerome K. (Jerome Klapka), 1859-1927, undated (Box 7, Folder 372)
    - King, Alice, 1886 (Box 7, Folder 373)
    - L.E.L. (Letitia Elizabeth Landon), 1802-1838, undated (Box 7, Folder 374)
    - Lee, Samuel, 1783-1852, undated (Box 7, Folder 375)
    - Leuville, William Redivivus Oliver de Lorncourt, Marquis de, b. 1843, 1881, undated (Box 7, Folder 376)
    - Lever, Charles James, 1806-1872, undated (Box 7, Folder 377)
    - Lind-af-Hageby, L. (Lizzy), 1878-1963, undated (Box 7, Folder 378)
    - Lyall, Edna, 1857-1903, 1893 (Box 7, Folder 379)
    - Lytton, Rosina Bulwer Lytton, Baroness, 1802-1882, 1849 (Box 7, Folder 380)
    - Mahan, A.T. (Alfred Thayer), 1840-1914, undated (Box 7, Folder 381)
    - Malet, Lucas, 1852-1931
      Related Archival Materials note
      See: Harrison, Mary St. Leger Kingsley, 1852-1931
    - Marryat, Florence, 1837-1899, 1869 (Box 7, Folder 382)
    - Martineau, Harriet, 1802-1876, 1859-60 (Box 7, Folder 383)
    - Michelsen, Edward H., 1848 (Box 7, Folder 384)
    - Millman, Henry Hart, 1791-1868, undated (Box 7, Folder 385)
    - Montgomery, James, 1771-1854, undated (Box 7, Folder 386)
    - Montgomery, Robert, 1807-1855, 1841, undated (Box 7, Folder 387)
    - Moore, Thomas, 1779-1852, undated (Box 7, Folder 388)
    - More, Hannah, 1745-1833, undated (Box 7, Folder 389)
    - Muddock, James Edward Preston, 1843- 1934, 1893 (Box 7, Folder 390)
    - Muller, F. Max (Friedrich Max), 1823- 1900, undated (Box 7, Folder 391)
    - Nearing, Scott, 1883-, 1935 (Box 7, Folder 392)
    - Newton, C.T. (Charles Thomas), 1816- 1894, 1861-76 (Box 7, Folder 393)
    - Norris, W.E. (William Edward), 1847- 1925, 1892 (Box 7, Folder 394)
    - Osborn, Sherard, 1822-1875, 1869 (Box 7, Folder 395)
    - Parker, Gilbert, 1862-1932, undated (Box 7, Folder 396)
    - Pemberton, Max, Sir, 1863-1950, 1920 (Box 7, Folder 397)
    - Pococke, Edward, 1648-1727, 1709 (Box 7, Folder 398)
    - Porter, Jane, 1776-1850, undated (Box 7, Folder 399)
    - Rogers, Samuel, 1763-1855, 1800, undated (Box 7, Folder 400)
    - Sala, George Augustus, 1828-1895, 1887 (Box 7, Folder 401)
    - Seeley, Robert Benton, 1798-1886, 1875 (Box 7, Folder 402)
    - Sichel, Walter Sydney, 1855-1933, 1908-1909 (Box 7, Folder 403)
    - Sims, George Robert, 1847-1922, 1888-1916, undated (Box 7, Folder 404)
    - Southey, Robert, 1774-1843, undated (Box 7, Folder 405)
    - Taylor, Tom, 1817-1880, 1858-63 (Box 7, Folder 406)
    - Tupper, Martin Farquhar, 1810-1889, 1848 (Box 7, Folder 407)
    - Vaughan, C.J. (Charles John), 1816- 1897, 1852 (Box 7, Folder 408)
    - Waterton, Charles, 1782-1865, 1829-52, undated (Box 7, Folder 409)
    - Watson, John, 1850-1907, undated (Box 7, Folder 410)
    - Wilson, John, 1785-1854, undated (Box 7, Folder 411)
    - Wright, Thomas, 1810-1877, 1840-62, undated (Box 7, Folder 412)
    - Yonge, Charlotte Mary, 1823-1901, undated (Box 7, Folder 413)
  - CIRCUS FIGURES
    - Astley's Circus, undated (Box 8, Folder 414)
    - Barnum, P.T. (Phineas Taylor), 1810- 1891, undated (Box 8, Folder 415)
    - Belzoni, Giovanni Battista, 1778-1823, undated (Box 8, Folder 416)
    - Bunker, Chang, 1811-1874 and Bunker, Eng, 1811-1874, undated (Box 8, Folder 417)
    - Cavanagh, Bernard, undated (Box 8, Folder 418)
    - Cheo, Louis, undated (Box 8, Folder 419)
    - "Chinese Dwarf", undated (Box 8, Folder 420)
    - Hinton, Turnour Thomas William, Viscount, 1849-1909, 1878 (Box 8, Folder 421)
    - Huline, W., 1864 (Box 8, Folder 422)
    - Matthews, Thomas, 1805-1889, 1873 (Box 8, Folder 423)
    - McDermott, Thomas, 1830 (Box 8, Folder 424)
    - Milnno, J., 1863-73 (Box 8, Folder 425)
    - Paap, Simon, undated (Box 8, Folder 426)
    - Payne, Harry, 1886 (Box 8, Folder 427)
    - Pond, Charles, 1911 (Box 8, Folder 428)
    - Ragoli Brothers, undated (Box 8, Folder 429)
    - Sandow, Eugene, 1867-1925, undated (Box 8, Folder 430)
    - Sanger, George, 1825-1911, 1885-1902, undated (Box 8, Folder 431)
    - Sheveneti, L., undated (Box 8, Folder 432)
  - CLERGY
    - Alford, Henry, 1810-1871, 1866 (Box 9, Folder 433)
    - Atkinson, Thomas, 1807-1881, 1866 (Box 9, Folder 434)
    - Atlay, John, 1817-1894, 1878 (Box 9, Folder 435)
    - Bennett, William J.E. (William James Early), 1804-1886, 1840 (Box 9, Folder 436)
    - Benson, Edward White, 1829-1896, 1882-92 (Box 9, Folder 437)
    - Brent, Charles Henry, 1862-1929, 1912 (Box 9, Folder 438)
    - Bromfield, Charles James, 1786-1857, 1834-47 (Box 9, Folder 439)
    - Brooks, Phillips, 1835-1893, 1884-92 (Box 9, Folder 440)
    - Browne, Edward Harold, 1811-1891, 1877 (Box 9, Folder 441)
    - Burgon, John William, 1813-1888, 1886 (Box 9, Folder 442)
    - Capel, T.J. (Thomas John), 1836-1911, 1881 (Box 9, Folder 443)
    - Carpenter, William Boyd, 1841-1918, 1891-1906, undated (Box 9, Folder 444)
    - Chapman, J. Wilbur (John Wilbur), 1859-1918, 1900 (Box 9, Folder 445)
    - Drummond, Henry, 1851-1897, 1885 (Box 9, Folder 446)
    - Duckworth, Robinson, 1834-1911, 1869-95 (Box 9, Folder 447)
    - Eden, George Rodney, 1853-1940, 1895 (Box 9, Folder 448)
    - Ellicott, C.J. (Charles John), 1819- 1905, 1843 (Box 9, Folder 449)
    - Gilbert, Ashurst Turner, 1786-1870, 1844 (Box 9, Folder 450)
    - Gladstone, Stephen Edward, 1844-1920, 1895 (Box 9, Folder 451)
    - Gorham, George Cornelius, 1787-1857, 1855 (Box 9, Folder 452)
    - Hallman, Newman, 1816-1902, 1868-91, undated (Box 9, Folder 453)
    - Holland, Henry Scott, 1847-1918, 1906, undated (Box 9, Folder 454)
    - Knox-Little, W.J. (William John), 1839-1918, undated (Box 9, Folder 455)
    - Lock, Walter, 1846-1933, 1898-1905 (Box 9, Folder 456)
    - Longley, Charles Thomas, 1794-1868, 1844 (Box 9, Folder 457)
    - Luxmoore, John, 1756-1830, 1808 (Box 9, Folder 458)
    - Mackarness, John Fielder, Bp. of Oxford, 1820-1889, 1874-87 (Box 9, Folder 459)
    - MacKonochie, A.H., 1825-1887, 1868-71 (Box 9, Folder 460)
    - Maclagen, William Dalrymple, Archbishop of York, 1826-1910, 1901 (Box 9, Folder 461)
    - Maguire, Robert, 1826-1890, 1875 (Box 9, Folder 462)
    - Marsh, Herbert, 1757-1839, 1819 (Box 9, Folder 463)
    - Marshall, T. Outram, b. 1843, 1895-96 (Box 9, Folder 464)
    - Maturin, B.W. (Basil William), 1847- 1915, 1896 (Box 9, Folder 465)
    - Maurice, Frederick Denison, 1805-1872, undated (Box 9, Folder 466)
    - Meyrick, Frederick, 1827-1906, 1875 (Box 9, Folder 467)
    - Milman, Henry Hart, 1791-1868, undated (Box 9, Folder 468)
    - Morison, John, 1826-1893, 1855 (Box 9, Folder 469)
    - Musgrave, Thomas, 1788-1860, 1853, undated (Box 9, Folder 470)
    - Newland, Henry, 1804-1860, 1855 (Box 9, Folder 471)
    - Noel, Baptist Wriothesley, 1798-1873, 1840-69, undated (Box 9, Folder 472)
    - Northcote, J. Spencer (James Spencer), 1821-1907, 1869 (Box 9, Folder 473)
    - Ogilvie, Charles A. (Charles Atmore), 1793-1873, 1871 (Box 9, Folder 474)
    - O'Sullivan, Mortimer, 1791?-1859, 1841 (Box 9, Folder 475)
    - Paget, Francis, 1851-1911, 1887-1905, undated (Box 9, Folder 476)
    - Palmer, Edwin, 1824-1895, 1889, undated (Box 9, Folder 477)
    - Palmer, Raymond, 1900 (Box 9, Folder 478)
    - Parker, Joseph, 1830-1902, undated (Box 9, Folder 479)
    - Parker, William, 1839 (Box 9, Folder 480)
    - Parry, Edward, Bp. of Dover, 1830-1890, 1871-89, undated (Box 9, Folder 481)
    - Parsons, James, 1797-1877, 1844-72 (Box 9, Folder 482)
    - Peacock, George, 1791-1858, undated (Box 9, Folder 483)
    - Pearse, Guy Mark, 1842-1930, 1887-90 (Box 9, Folder 484)
    - Pearson, Hugh, 1817-1882, 1871 (Box 9, Folder 485)
    - Pennefeather, William, 1816-1873, 1870 (Box 9, Folder 486)
    - Percy, Hugh, 1784-1856, 1853-56, undated (Box 9, Folder 487)
    - Phelan, C.E., 1835 (Box 9, Folder 488)
    - Phillips, E.C., 1877-81 (Box 9, Folder 489)
    - Phillpotts, Henry, 1778-1869, 1828-65, undated (Box 9, Folder 490)
    - Philpott, Henry, 1807-1892, 1858-60 (Box 9, Folder 491)
    - Plunket, Thomas Span Plunket, Baron, 1792-1866, 1850 (Box 9, Folder 492)
    - Plunket, William Conyngham Plunket, Baron, 1828-1897, 1884-85, undated (Box 9, Folder 493)
    - Pollen, John Hungerford, 1820-1902, 1900, undated (Box 9, Folder 494)
    - Portal, G.R., 1888 (Box 9, Folder 495)
    - Pott, Alfred, 1822-1908, 1891 (Box 9, Folder 496)
    - Randolph, B.W. (Berkeley William), 1858-1925, 1900 (Box 9, Folder 497)
    - Richards, W. Upton, 1872 (Box 9, Folder 498)
    - Rogers, John, 1873 (Box 9, Folder 499)
    - Rowley, Henry, 1865, undated (Box 9, Folder 500)
    - Rowsell, Thomas J., 1816-1894, 1854 (Box 9, Folder 501)
    - Russell, Wriothesley, Lord, 1804-1886, undated (Box 9, Folder 502)
    - Ryan, Vincent William, 1816-1888, 1860 (Box 9, Folder 503)
    - Scott, C.P. (Charles Perry), 1847-1927, 1900, undated (Box 10, Folder 504)
    - Seymour, M. Hobart (Michael Hobart), 1800-1874, 1851-68, undated (Box 10, Folder 505)
    - Singer, Simeon, 1848-1906, 1889 (Box 10, Folder 506)
    - Smith, George, 1844 (Box 10, Folder 507)
    - Smith, John Pye, 1774-1851, 1838-42, undated (Box 10, Folder 508)
    - Smytham, George Hunt, 1859 (Box 10, Folder 509)
    - Spencer, George, 1799-1864, 1846 (Box 10, Folder 510)
    - Spurgeon, C.H. (Charles Haddon), 1834- 1892, 1884 (Box 10, Folder 511)
    - Stamford, C., 1881 (Box 10, Folder 512)
    - Stanley, Arthur Penrhyn, 1815-1881, 1861-81, undated (Box 10, Folder 513)
    - Stanton, A.H. (Arthur Henry), 1839- 1913, 1882-92, undated (Box 10, Folder 514)
    - Stanton, V.H. (Vincent Henry), 1846- 1924, 1892 (Box 10, Folder 515)
    - Stebbing, Henry, 1799-1883, undated (Box 10, Folder 516)
    - Stock, Eugene, 1836-1928, 1894 (Box 10, Folder 517)
    - Stone, S.J. (Samuel John), 1839-1900, 1876-91 (Box 10, Folder 518)
    - Stoughton, John, 1807-1897, undated (Box 10, Folder 519)
    - Stovel, Charles, 1799-1883, 1853 (Box 10, Folder 520)
    - Strachan, J.M. (John Miller), 1832- 1903, 1883-99 (Box 10, Folder 521)
    - Stubbs, William, 1825-1901, undated (Box 10, Folder 522)
    - Sumner, John Bird, 1780-1862, 1848-60, undated (Box 10, Folder 523)
    - Symons, B.P. (Benjamin Parsons), 1785-1878, 1870 (Box 10, Folder 524)
    - Tatham, Ralph, 1852 (Box 10, Folder 525)
    - Thirwall, Connop, 1797-1875, 1852 (Box 10, Folder 526)
    - Todd, Henry James, 1763-1845, undated (Box 10, Folder 527)
    - Tomlinson, George, d. 1863, 1842 (Box 10, Folder 528)
    - Tottenham, Edward, 1810-1853, 1842 (Box 10, Folder 529)
    - Trench, Francis, 1805-1886, 1864 (Box 10, Folder 530)
    - Trench, Richard Chenevix, 1807-1886, 1848-62, undated (Box 10, Folder 531)
    - Tucker, H.W. (Henry William), 1830- 1902, 1888-97 (Box 10, Folder 532)
    - Turton, Thomas, 1780-1864, 1845-53 (Box 10, Folder 533)
    - Tyler, James Endell, 1789-1851, undated (Box 10, Folder 534)
    - Underhill, Edward Bean, 1813-1901, 1866 (Box 10, Folder 535)
    - Vaughan, Robert, 1795-1868, 1860-62 (Box 10, Folder 536)
    - Vernon-Harcourt, Edward Venables, 1757-1847, undated (Box 10, Folder 537)
    - Views of the bishop's residence, undated (Box 10, Folder 538)
    - Villiers, H. Montagu (Henry Montagu), 1813-1861, 1860, undated (Box 10, Folder 539)
    - Villiers, Henry Montagu, 1837-1908, undated (Box 10, Folder 540)
    - Vores, Thomas, 1872 (Box 10, Folder 541)
    - Voysey, Charles, 1828-1912, 1897-1906 (Box 10, Folder 542)
    - Waggett, P.N. (Philip Napier), 1862- 1939, 1900 (Box 10, Folder 543)
    - Waldegrave, Samuel, 1817-1869, 1861-66, undated (Box 10, Folder 544)
    - Watkins, H.G., 1843 (Box 10, Folder 545)
    - Way, Charles, 1851 (Box 10, Folder 546)
    - Weaver, Richard, undated (Box 10, Folder 547)
    - Webb-Peploe, Hanmer William, 1837-1923, 1905, undated (Box 10, Folder 548)
    - Westcott, Brooke Foss, 1825-1901, 1898-1901 (Box 10, Folder 549)
    - Whately, Richard, 1787-1863, 1848-56, undated (Box 10, Folder 550)
    - Whitaker, G.H., 1884 (Box 10, Folder 551)
    - White, Edward, 1819-1898, 1896 (Box 10, Folder 552)
    - White-Thompson, Leonard Jauncey, b. 1863, undated (Box 10, Folder 553)
    - Wilberforce, Basil (Alfred Basil Orme), 1841-1916, 1902-06, undated (Box 10, Folder 554)
    - Wilberforce, Samuel, 1805-1873, 1846-70, undated (Box 10, Folder 555)
    - Wilkinson, George Howard, 1833-1907, 1875-87 (Box 10, Folder 556)
    - Williams, Z. de K., 1894 (Box 10, Folder 557)
    - Wilson, Daniel, 1778-1858, 1843-53, undated (Box 10, Folder 558)
    - Wiseman, Nicholas Patrick, 1802-1865, 1841, undated (Box 10, Folder 559)
    - Woodford, James Russell, 1820-1885, 1873-82, undated (Box 10, Folder 560)
    - Wynter, Philip, 1793-1871, undated (Box 10, Folder 561)
  - CRIME, PRISONS AND REFORM
    - Arrow, Charles, 1904 (Box 11, Folder 562)
    - Bishop, Thomas, 1831 (Box 11, Folder 563)
    - Bradford, Edward Ridley Colborne, Sir, bart., 1836-1911, 1893 (Box 11, Folder 564)
    - Brooke, Lord, 1843-1891, undated (Box 11, Folder 565)
    - Buchanan, Francis, undated (Box 11, Folder 566)
    - Bury St. Edmund's Gaol, 1705 (Box 11, Folder 567)
    - Cochon de Lapparent, Charles, 1750- 1825, 1794 (Box 11, Folder 568)
    - Cornish, W.O., 1929 (Box 11, Folder 569)
    - Fitch, Francis, b. 1860, 1807 (Box 11, Folder 570)
    - Fry, Elizabeth, 1780-1845, 1822-36 (Box 11, Folder 571)
    - Griffiths, Arthur, 1838-1908, 1903 (Box 11, Folder 572)
    - Harvey, D.W. (Daniel Whittle), 1786- 1863, 1843 (Box 11, Folder 573)
    - Henry, E.R. (Edward Richard), Sir, 1850-1931, undated (Box 11, Folder 574)
    - Henry, Thomas, Sir, 1807-1876, undated (Box 11, Folder 575)
    - House of Correction, Middlesex County, undated (Box 11, Folder 576)
    - King's Bench and Marshalsea Prisons, 1828 (Box 11, Folder 577)
    - Lane, Richard Ouseley Blake, b. 1842, 1908 (Box 11, Folder 578)
    - Mansell, Susanna Maria, 1837 (Box 11, Folder 579)
    - Money, Leo George Chiozza, Sir, 1870- 1944, 1908 (Box 11, Folder 580)
    - Newburn, 1821 (Box 11, Folder 581)
    - Orton, Arthur, 1834-1898, undated (Box 11, Folder 582)
    - Pook, Edmund Walter, 1872 (Box 11, Folder 583)
    - Roughead, William, 1870-1952, undated (Box 11, Folder 584)
    - Ruggles-Brise, Evelyn John, Sir, 1857- 1935, 1901 (Box 11, Folder 585)
    - Rush, John Blomfield, d. 1849, undated (Box 11, Folder 586)
    - St. Ives, County of Cornwall, Court Case, 1831 (Box 11, Folder 587)
    - Salisbury, James Brownlow William Gascoyne-Cecil, Marquess of, 1791-1868, undated (Box 11, Folder 588)
    - Stirling, T.H. (Thomas Henry), 1789- 1864, 1823 (Box 11, Folder 589)
    - Thomson, Basil, 1861-1939, 1921 (Box 11, Folder 590)
    - Unidentified, 1849 (Box 11, Folder 591)
    - Unidentified, undated (Box 11, Folder 592)
    - Vincent, C.E. Howard (Charles Edward Howard), 1849-1908, 1882-84 (Box 11, Folder 593)
    - Wensley, Frederick Porter, 1865-1949, 1911 (Box 11, Folder 594)
    - Wharncliffe, James Archibald Stuart- Wortley-Mackenzie, Baron, 1776-1845, 1837 (Box 11, Folder 595)
  - JEWISH HISTORY
    - Adler, Nettie, 1904 (Box 12, Folder 596)
    - Angerstein, John Julius William, 1800- 1866, 1841 (Box 12, Folder 597)
    - Bernal-Osborne, Ralph, 1802-1882, undated (Box 12, Folder 598)
    - Da Costa, Solomon, 1762-63 (Box 12, Folder 599)
    - Elmslie, W.A.L. (William Alexander Leslie), 1925 (Box 12, Folder 600)
    - Ginsburg, Christian D. (Christian David), 1831-1914, undated (Box 12, Folder 601)
    - Goldsmid, Isaac L. (Isaac Lyon), 1778- 1859, 1848 (Box 12, Folder 602)
    - Gordon, Samuel, 1871-1927, 1907 (Box 12, Folder 603)
    - Hoffman, David, 1784-1854, 1853 (Box 12, Folder 604)
    - Jacobs, Joseph, 1854-1916, 1899 (Box 12, Folder 605)
    - Kent, Madeleine, 1938 (Box 12, Folder 606)
    - Monteforce, C.G. (Claude Goldsmid), 1858-1938, undated (Box 12, Folder 607)
    - Smith, W. Robertson (William Robertson), 1846-1894, 1877 (Box 12, Folder 608)
    - Waley-Cohen, Ina, undated (Box 12, Folder 609)
    - Woelff, J., 1805 (Box 12, Folder 610)
    - Wolf, Lucien, 1857-1930, 1903 (Box 12, Folder 611)
    - Zangwill, Israel, 1864-1926, 1915-17 (Box 12, Folder 612)
    - Zea, F.A., 1821 (Box 12, Folder 613)
  - LEGAL FIGURES
    - Birkett, Norman Birkett, Baron, 1883- 1962, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 614)
    - Bovill, William, 1814-1873, undated (Box 13, Folder 615)
    - Brampton, Henry Hawkins, Baron, 1817- 1907, 1863-69, undated (Box 13, Folder 616)
    - Brown, James Clifton, b. 1841, undated (Box 13, Folder 617)
    - Clarke, Edward George, Sir, 1841-1931, 1884 (Box 13, Folder 618)
    - Cockburn, Alexander James Edmund, Sir, 1802-1880, 1850-65, undated (Box 13, Folder 619)
    - Coleridge, John Taylor, Sir, 1790-1876, 1850 (Box 13, Folder 620)
    - Court summons, City and Liberty of Westminster, 1819 (Box 13, Folder 621)
    - Courts admittance ticket, 1810 (Box 13, Folder 622)
    - Darling, Charles J. Darling (Charles John Darling), Baron, 1849-1936, undated (Box 13, Folder 623)
    - Ellenborough, Edward Law, Baron, 1750- 1818, 1815-16 (Box 13, Folder 624)
    - Esher, William Balliol Brett, Viscount, 1815-1899, 1870 (Box 13, Folder 625)
    - Goldsmid, Francis Henry, Sir, 1808- 1878, 1861 (Box 13, Folder 626)
    - Halifax, Dunk, 1705-1793, 1763 (Box 13, Folder 627)
    - Hastings, Patrick, Sir, 1880-1952, undated (Box 13, Folder 628)
    - Hatherley, William Page Wood, Baron, 1801-1881, 1869-80 (Box 13, Folder 629)
    - Hill, Matthew Davenport, 1792-1872, 1857 (Box 13, Folder 630)
    - Jury service summons, 1879 (Box 13, Folder 631)
    - Legal case, Mandrell v. Mandrell, 1819 (Box 13, Folder 632)
    - Levi, Leone, 1821-1888, 1860 (Box 13, Folder 633)
    - Maclean, Francis William, Sir, 1844- 1913, 1887 (Box 13, Folder 634)
    - Macnaghten, Edward, Baron, 1830-1913, 1887 (Box 13, Folder 635)
    - Macnaghten, Melville L. (Melville Leslie), Sir, 1853-1921, 1894 (Box 13, Folder 636)
    - Manistry, Henry, 1808-1890, 1885 (Box 13, Folder 637)
    - Mansfield, James, Sir, 1733-1821, 1813 (Box 13, Folder 638)
    - Mathew, James Charles, Sir, 1830-1908, undated (Box 13, Folder 639)
    - May, Thomas Erskine, 1815-1886, 1879 (Box 13, Folder 640)
    - Mayne, Richard, 1796-1868, 1854 (Box 13, Folder 641)
    - Monckton, John Braddick, Sir, 1832- 1902, 1896-1902 (Box 13, Folder 642)
    - Monkswell, Robert Collier, Baron, 1845-1909, 1890 (Box 13, Folder 643)
    - Morris and Killanin, Michael Morris, Baron, 1827-1901, 1887 (Box 13, Folder 644)
    - Moulton, J. Fletcher (John Fletcher), 1844-1921, 1895 (Box 13, Folder 645)
    - Parkes, William, undated (Box 13, Folder 646)
    - Parry, John Humffreys, 1816-1880, 1852-76 (Box 13, Folder 647)
    - Patterson, John, Sir, 1790-1861, 1821-61, undated (Box 13, Folder 648)
    - Payne, John Horne, 1837-1920, 1864 (Box 13, Folder 649)
    - Pennefather, Alfred Richard, Sir, b. 1845, undated (Box 13, Folder 650)
    - Phillimore, John George, 1808-1865, 1853-59 (Box 13, Folder 651)
    - Phillimore, Joseph, 1775-1855, 1827 (Box 13, Folder 652)
    - Phillimore, Walter G.F. Phillimore (Walter George Frank Phillimore), Baron, 1845-1929, 1887-1900 (Box 13, Folder 653)
    - Plumtre, Charles John, 1818-1887, 1890 (Box 13, Folder 654)
    - Pollock, Charles Edward, Sir, 1823- 1897, 1893, undated (Box 13, Folder 655)
    - Pollock, F. (Frederick), Sir, 1783- 1870, 1853-67 (Box 13, Folder 656)
    - Pollock, William Frederick, Sir, 1815- 1888, 1840 (Box 13, Folder 657)
    - Pulling, Alexander, 1813-1895, undated (Box 13, Folder 658)